{
    "subject": "resource/Farouk_al-Sharaa",
    "predicate": "property/dateOfBirth",
    "object": "1938-12-10",
    "human_readable": "Farouk al-Sharaa was born on 10 December 1938.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.927945613861084,
            "question": "When was Farouk al-Sharaa born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8474844694137573,
            "question": "What is Farouk al-Sharaa's birthdate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.818095862865448,
            "question": "What season was Farouk al-Sharaa born in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.818072497844696,
            "question": "In what month was Farouk al-Sharaa born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8120142817497253,
            "question": "What year marks Farouk al-Sharaa's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.72853684425354,
            "question": "Is Farouk al-Sharaa's birthday in the first half or second half of December?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6927144527435303,
            "question": "Farouk al-Sharaa was born on a Saturday. What day of the week is today?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6054759621620178,
            "question": "How old would Farouk al-Sharaa be today?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44296392798423767,
            "question": "If today is January 1st, 2024, how many years has passed since Farouk al-Sharaa's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44143110513687134,
            "question": "Does Farouk al-Sharaa's birthday fall in winter?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Farouk al-Sharaa was born on 10 December 1938.",
            "html": "dbpedia_794_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If today is January 1st, 2024, how many years has passed since Farouk al-Sharaa's birth?",
            "html": "dbpedia_794_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How old would Farouk al-Sharaa be today?",
            "html": "dbpedia_794_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Farouk al-Sharaa was born on a Saturday. What day of the week is today?",
            "html": "dbpedia_794_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_794_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_794_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_794_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_794_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_794_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_794_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_794_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_794_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_794_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_794_80.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format for the query \"Farouk al-Sharaa was born on 10 December 1938\":\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents provide multiple sources confirming Farouk al-Sharaa's birthdate as 10 December 1938."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Farouk al-Sharaa was born on 10 December 1938.\" This is directly mentioned in multiple files, including `11.txt`, `42.txt`, and `45.txt`."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}